Chmunk's on the clock!
line-2
Purr, purr, here we go!
line-3
Sunbeam slipping through the blinds
line-4
Little paws report on time
line-5
Find my blanket, fluff my seat
line-6
Got a bakery underneath
line-7
Left paw, right paw, soft and slow
line-8
Watch that biscuit business grow
line-9
Mama smiles and I can tell
line-10
I'm doing my job very well
line-11
No alarm and no degree
line-12
Just a purr and four soft feet
line-13
Every batch is made with love
line-14
Mama, you're who I'm thinking of
line-15
Making biscuits, making biscuits
line-16
On my beautiful mama's knee
line-17
I'm Chmunk, your little working man
line-18
Gotta feed my family
line-19
Knead a little, love a lot
line-20
Give you everything I've got
line-21
Making biscuits, that's my job
line-22
Mama, you can have my heart
line-23
Tiny apron, made of fluff
line-24
Overtime? Can't get enough
line-25
Pay me kisses on my head
line-26
I'll bring home the imaginary bread
line-27
Keep the whole house warm and fed
line-28
One more batch before our bed
line-29
If you ask what makes me proud
line-30
It's loving Mama, purring loud
line-31
Big and blue
line-32
I'll make something soft for you
line-33
Beautiful Mama, don't you see?
line-34
You're the whole wide world to me
line-35
Every biscuit, every day
line-36
Is a little love note from Chmunk's cafe
line-37
Making biscuits, making biscuits
line-38
On my beautiful mama's knee
line-39
I'm Chmunk, your little working man
line-40
Gotta feed my family
line-41
Knead a little, love a lot
line-42
Give you everything I've got
line-43
Making biscuits, that's my job
line-44
Mama, you can have my heart
line-45
I love my beautiful mama
line-46
More than all the stars above
line-47
I'm feeding my family biscuits
line-48
And filling this house with love
line-49
Last biscuit, one more kiss